listproxysites.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy for ListProxySites.com

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at ListProxySites.com. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. This privacy policy may be subject to change without notice at any time.

## Log Files

We use log files to track all visits to ListProxySites.com. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user's movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information but may be traceable by your ISP. We may be legally required to make log files and other details available, in the event that we are asked to release such information by proper authorities we will do so. If we suspect that any illegal activity is going on then we reserve the right to forward any such details to the proper authorities and law enforcement officials voluntarily. We will not condone or support any illegal activities.

## Cookies

We use cookies to remember your login and visit details. Advertising services such as Google Adsense also use cookies. We have no access to and cannot control these cookies. For more information on controlling cookies for your particular browser please go to [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed instructions, or use your browser "Help" button (usually 'F1').

## Beacons

This site does not use beacons, however, advertising services such Google Adsense may use beacons. We have no access to and cannot control these beacons or their logs.

## Advertisers and Affiliate Companies

ListProxySites.com uses outside ad companies to display ads, such as Google Adsense. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. To the best of our knowledge, we follow all ad and affiliate company privacy policies. Please check their websites for the respective privacy policies.

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/ "https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/"). Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policy, that can be found here: [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google's Privacy Policy").

## Email Addresses

ListProxySites.com requires your email address when you submit a proxy site for listing, register for a free account or use the contact form, this is for verification purposes only and the email address you give us will never be given, sold, leased or rented out to any third parties. Your email address will be stored securely in our database and any passwords are encrypted so not even we can read them. We may use your email address to inform you when your proxy is accepted or rejected or if you send us a message it may be used to reply to you. It may also be used to notify you of any important site or account changes. We also require a valid email address if you sign up for our Google Group. We will NOT send you details of any 'special offers' or other spam like emails ever! We hate spam as much if not more than you, so your details will be safe with us.

## Outgoing Links

ListProxySites.com contains links to other world wide web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any other sites we link to. We encourage our visitors to be aware that when they leave ListProxySites.com to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that is visited. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by ListProxySites.com.

Also see our Terms of Use.

[Visitors](http://statcounter.com/p6924447/summary/?guest=1 "View Our Website Visitor Statistics"):
